{"data":[{"question":"Is Susan ________ home?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","d":"under","answer":"2","explain":"\n- At home: fixed expression","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Do the children go to school every day? \"________\"","a":"Yes, they go.","b":"Yes, they do.","c":"They go.","d":"No, they don't go.","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When replying to a yes\/no question, we can use the auxiliary instead of repeating the full verb.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"What ________ now?","a":"is the time","b":"does the time","c":"is time","d":"is it","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Use \"what's the time\" to ask about time.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"They always go to school ________ bicycle.","a":"with","b":"in","c":"on","d":"by","answer":"4","explain":"\n- By...: means using a particular method or transport\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"What color ________ his new car?","a":"have","b":"is","c":"does","d":"are","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We need a verb (is) to fill in the blank","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Are there many students in Room 12? \"________\"","a":"Yes there are.","b":"Yes, they are.","c":"Some are.","d":"No they aren't.","answer":"1","explain":"\n- When replying yes to a yes\/no question: yes, S + auxiliary","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"You should do your ________ before going to class.","a":"home work","b":"homework","c":"homeworks","d":"housework","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Homework: work that a student at school is asked to do at home (uncountable noun).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr.Pike ________ us English.","a":"teach","b":"teaches","c":"teaching","d":"to teach","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Subject (Mr Pike) is singular.\u00a0\n- When a verb ends in a sibilant sound such as ch, s, sh, x or z, the letter e is added before the s ending.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Tom and ________ are going to the birthday party together.","a":"I","b":"me","c":"my","d":"mine","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Use I (pronoun) as the subject in the sentence","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Our English lessons are ________ long.","a":"many","b":"much","c":"a lot of","d":"very","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Very: used as an adverb before adjectives","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}